<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<labels 				xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" 
								xmlns:proviso="http://geonetwork-opensource.org/schemas/prov-xml/proviso/1.0/2015-04-14"
								xmlns:prov="http://www.w3.org/ns/prov#">
    <element name="prov:id">
        <label>ID</label>
        <description>Must be in the form of an XML Qualified Name eg. gnprov:dataset1 - must also be unique. Note qualified names have an optional prefix (in front of the :) and a name part (after the :). The prefix and name parts must start with a letter and be alphanumeric.</description>
    </element>
    <element name="prov:ref">
        <label>Reference to ID</label>
        <description>Must be a reference to an ID in the form of an XML Qualified Name eg. gnprov:dataset1 - must also be unique. Note qualified names have an optional prefix (in front of the :) and a name part (after the :). The prefix and name parts must start with a letter and be alphanumeric.</description>
    </element>
    <element name="prov:document">
        <label>Provenance Document</label>
        <description></description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:label">
        <label>Label</label>
        <description>The label is a human-readable representation of an instance of a PROV-DM type or relation.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:location">
        <label>Location</label>
        <description>A location can be an identifiable geographic place (ISO 19112), but it can also be a non-geographic place such as a directory, row, or column. </description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:type">
        <label>Type</label>
        <description>The type provides further typing information for any construct with an optional set of attribute-value pairs. </description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:value">
        <label>Value</label>
        <description>The value is a direct representation of an entity as a PROV-DM Value.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:role">
        <label>Role</label>
        <description>A role is the function of an entity or agent with respect to an activity, in the context of a usage, generation, invalidation, association, start, and end.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:startTime">
        <label>Start Time</label>
        <description>Start time for an activity.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:endTime">
        <label>End Time</label>
        <description>End time for an activity.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:time">
        <label>Time</label>
        <description>Time stamp.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:entity">
        <label>Entity</label>
        <description>An entity is a physical, digital, conceptual, or other kind of thing with some fixed aspects; entities may be real or imaginary. In this implementation: an entity is a parameter for an OGC Web Processing Service to consume or the output of an OGC Web Processing Service. If the parameter is a dataset and a metadata record exists for that dataset then the prov:id of the entity will be set to the uuid of that metadata record.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:activity">
        <label>Activity</label>
        <description>An activity is something that occurs over a period of time and acts upon or with entities; it may        include consuming, processing, transforming, modifying, relocating, using, or generating entities. In this implementation, the prov:id attribute can be set to the uuid of a metadata record describing the activity (usually with metadataScopeCode set to project)</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasGeneratedBy">
        <label>Was Generated By</label>
        <description>Describes the completion of production of a new entity by an activity. This entity did not exist before generation and becomes available for usage after this generation.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:used">
        <label>Used</label>
        <description>Describes the usage of an entity by an activity. Before usage, the activity had not begun to utilize this entity and could not have been affected by the entity.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasInformedBy">
        <label>Was Informed By</label>
        <description>Describes how an activity uses an entity generated by a different activity.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasStartedBy">
        <label>Was Started By</label>
        <description>Describes when an activity is started by an entity known as trigger.  The activity did not exist before its start. Any usage, generation, or invalidation involving an activity follows the activity's start. A start may refer to a trigger entity that set off the activity, or to an activity, known as starter, that generated the trigger. In this implementation a trigger entity could be a command to submit a collection of entities to an OGC Web Processing Service.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasEndedBy">
        <label>Was Ended By</label>
        <description>Describes when an activity is ended by an entity known as trigger. The activity no longer exists after its end. Any usage, generation, or invalidation involving an activity precedes the activity's end. An end may refer to a trigger entity that terminated the activity, or to an activity, known as ender that generated the trigger.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasInvalidatedBy">
        <label>Was Invalidated By</label>
        <description>Invalidation is the start of the destruction, cessation, or expiry of an existing entity by an activity. The entity is no longer available for use (or further invalidation) after invalidation. Any generation or usage of an entity precedes its invalidation.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasDerivedFrom">
        <label>Was Derived From</label>
        <description>A derivation is a transformation of an entity into another, an update of an entity resulting in a new one, or the construction of a new entity based on a pre-existing entity.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasRevisionOf">
        <label>Was Revision Of</label>
        <description>A revision is a derivation for which the resulting entity is a revised version of some original.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasQuotedFrom">
        <label>Was Quoted From</label>
        <description>A quotation is the repeat of (some or all of) an entity, such as text or image, by someone who may or may not be its original author.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:hadPrimarySource">
        <label>Had Primary Source</label>
        <description>A primary source for a topic refers to something produced by some agent with direct experience and knowledge about the topic, at the time of the topic's study, without benefit from hindsight.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:agent">
        <label>Agent</label>
        <description>An agent is something that bears some form of responsibility for an activity taking place, for the existence of an entity, or for another agent's activity. In this implementation: an agent has a prov:id which points to an ISO metadata fragment (eg. cit:CI_Organisation for ISO19115-1/-3)</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:person">
        <label>Person</label>
        <description>Person agents are people. In this implementation: a person has a prov:id which points to an ISO metadata fragment (eg. cit:CI_Individual for ISO19115-1/-3)</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:organization">
        <label>Organisation</label>
        <description>An organization is a social or legal institution such as a company, society, etc. In this implementation: an organization has a prov:id which points to an ISO metadata fragment (eg. cit:CI_Organisation for ISO19115-1/-3).</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:softwareAgent">
        <label>Software Agent</label>
        <description>A software agent is running software. In this implementation: a software agent has a prov:id which points to a metadata record that describes an OGC web processing service (WPS).</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasAttributedTo">
        <label>Was Attributed To</label>
        <description>Describes an attribution. Attribution is the ascribing of an entity to an agent.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasAssociatedWith">
        <label>Was Associated With</label>
        <description>An activity association is an assignment of responsibility to an agent for an activity, indicating that the agent had a role in the activity. It further allows for a plan to be specified, which is the plan intended by the agent to achieve some goals in the context of this activity.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:actedOnBehalfOf">
        <label>Acted On Behalf Of</label>
        <description>Describes a delegation. A delegation is the assignment of authority and responsibility to an agent (by itself or by another agent) to carry out a specific activity as a delegate or representative, while the agent it acts on behalf of retains some responsibility for the outcome of the delegated work.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:wasInfluencedBy">
        <label>Was Influenced By</label>
        <description>Describes influence. Influence is the capacity of an entity, activity, or agent to have an effect on the character, development, or behavior of another by means of usage, start, end, generation, invalidation, communication, derivation, attribution, association, or delegation.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:delegate">
        <label>Delegated Agent</label>
        <description>Delegated agent reference.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:responsible">
        <label>Responsible Agent</label>
        <description>Responsible agent reference.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:bundle">
        <label>Bundle</label>
        <description>A bundle is a named set of provenance descriptions, and is itself an ENTITY, so allowing provenance of provenance to be expressed.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:specializationOf">
        <label>Specialization Of</label>
        <description>An ENTITY that is a specialization of another shares all aspects of the latter, and additionally presents more specific aspects of the same thing as the latter. In particular, the lifetime of the entity being specialized contains that of any specialization.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:alternateOf">
        <label>Alternate Of</label>
        <description>Two alternate entities present aspects of the same thing. These aspects may be the same or different, and the alternate entities may or may not overlap in time.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:collection">
        <label>Collection</label>
        <description>A collection is an entity that provides a structure to some constituents that must themselves be entities. These constituents are said to be member of the collections.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:emptyCollection">
        <label>Empty Collection</label>
        <description>An empty collection is a collection without members. </description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:hadMember">
        <label>Had Member</label>
        <description></description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:plan">
        <label>Plan</label>
        <description>A plan is an entity that represents a set of actions or steps intended by one or more agents to achieve some goals.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="prov:other">
        <label>Document Metadata</label>
        <description>A block of elements that hold basic discovery metadata about the provenance document.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="dct:modified">
        <label>Date Modified</label>
        <description>Modification date of the provenance document.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="dct:created">
        <label>Date Created</label>
        <description>Creation date of the provenance document.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="dc:title">
        <label>Title</label>
        <description>Title of the provenance document.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="dc:description">
        <label>Abstract</label>
        <description>Description of the provenance document.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="dc:identifier">
        <label>Identifier</label>
        <description>Identifier of the provenance document.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="dc:coverage">
        <label>Bounding Box</label>
        <description>Bounding box of the provenance document.</description>
    </element>
		<element name="dc:subject">
        <label>Keywords</label>
        <description>Keywords that describe the provenance document.</description>
    </element>
</labels>
